Guide to the International Brotherhood of Teamsters Congressional Testimony collection 1897-1977 IBT0047
Special Collections Research Center, The George Washington University
IBT Congressional Testimony Collection
1897-1996
Special Collections Research Center, The George Washington University
International Brotherhood of Teamsters, Chauffeurs, Warehousemen, and Helpers of America
IBT0047
5 Linear Feet
This collection contains the congressional testimony of representitives of the International Brotherhood of Teamsters. There are statements from various representatives such as James R. Hoffa. The statements are before various committees in Congress. The dates range from 1987-1977.
Arrangement
Arranged chronologically
bib
MMS ID# 99128136553604107
Conditions Governing Access
This collection is open for research.
Scope and Contents
This collection contains the congressional testimony of representitives of the International Brotherhood of Teamsters. There are statements from various representatives such as James R. Hoffa. The statements are before various committees in Congress. The dates range from 1987-1977.
Labor unions -- United States -- History -- 20th century; Labor unions; Labor
- Statement Before Committee on Merchant Marine and Fisheries of The United States of Representitives, 1 May 1897; Series 1 (Box 1, Folder 1)
- Statement of Harold J Gibbons Executive Vice President International Brotherhood of Teamsters Before the Subcommittee on Unemployment and then Impact of Automation of the House Committee on Education and Labor, 12 April 1961; Series 1 (Box 1, Folder 2)
- Testimony on The National Highway Safety Act by James Riddle Hoffa General President, 1962-1963; Series 1 (Box 1, Folder 3)
- Statement Before Committee On The District Of Columbia U.S. Senate, 6 November 1963; Series 1 (Box 1, Folder 4)
- Supplemental Statement Submitted To Committee On Ways And Means Of The U.S. House Of Representatives, 11 March 1964; Series 1 (Box 1, Folder 5)
- Statement Before Select Subcommittee On Labor US House Of Representatives Statement By Sidney Zagri, Legislative Counsel IBT, 26 May 1965; Series 1 (Box 1, Folder 6)
- Attatchments To Statement Sidney Zagri IBT, 15 July 1965; Series 1 (Box 1, Folder 7)
- Statement Before Committee On Labor And Public Welfare United States Senate (Subcommittee on Labor), 15 July 1965; Series 1 (Box 1, Folder 8)
- Statement Before Subcommittee On Labor United States Senate Statment By Stanely M. Rosenblum, Attorney at Law IBT, 14 October 1966; Series 1 (Box 1, Folder 9)
- Statement Before Committee On Commerce US Senate Statement by James R Hoffa IBT, 6 April 1966; Series 1 (Box 1, Folder 10)
- Statement of Frank E Fitzsimmons General President, 25 March 1977; Series 1 (Box 1, Folder 11)
- Statements by Senators Samn Nuun and Charles Percy on the Teamsters union Central States Pension Fund Inquiry, March 30-September 10, 1976; Se4ries 1 (Box 2, Folder 1)
- Senate Hearings: Labor Union Insurance Investigation-Interrogatory of Frank E. Fritzsimmongs before Subcommittee on Investigations Transcripts [1], October 10, 1977; Series 1 (Box 2, Folder 2)
- Senate Hearings: Labor Union Insurance Investigation -News Clippings and Correspondence [2], October 11, 1977; Series 1 (Box 2, Folder 3)
- Senate Hearings: Labor Union Insurance Investigation-News Clippings and Correspondence [3], October 12, 1977; Series 1 (Box 2, Folder 4)
- Senate Hearings: Teamsters Union Insurance Testimonies before the Permament Subcommittee on Investigations Transcript, October 10, 1977; Series 1 (Box 2, Folder 5)
- Senate Hearings: Teamster Central States Pension Fund Task Force Transcript, July 18, 1977; Series 1 (Box 3, Folder 1)
- Senate Hearings: Teamster Central States Pension Fund Task Force Transcript, July 21, 1977; Series 1 (Box 3, Folder 2)
- Senate Hearings: Frank E. Fitzsimmons Statements in Executive Session before SubCommitte on Investigations, July 29, 1977; Series 1 (Box 3, Folder 3)
- Senate Hearings: Daniel J. Shannon Statements in Executive Session before SubCommittee on Investigations, July 29, 1977; Series 1 (Box 3, Folder 4)
- Securities and Exchange Commission versus National Pacific Corporation Civil Action No.76-1784 in the U.S. District Court for the District Columbia (J.Hauser), September 28, 1977; Series 1 (Box 3, Folder 5)
- Senate Hearings: Statement, correspondence, and newsclippings of Frank E. Fritzsimmons and Richard Gordon Kleindienst Testimony before Subcommittee on Investigations, October 25-November 2, 1977; Series 1 (Box 4, Folder 1)
- Senate HearingsL Labor Union Insurance Investigation-Opening Statements, Attached Materials, and Interrogatory of Richard C. Herran, Jr., October 28, 1977-September 1, 1977; Series 1 (Box 4, Folder 2)
- Senate Hearings: Testimony and Interrogatory of Daniel Shannon, September 2, 1977; Series 1 (Box 4, Folder 3)
- Senate Hearings: Labor Union Insurance Investigation Transcripts [1], October 10, 1977; Series 1 (Box 5, Folder 1)
- Senate HearingsL Labor Union Insurance Investigation Transcripts [2], October 11, 1977; Series 1 (Box 5, Folder 2)
- Senate Hearings: Labor Union Insurance Investigation Transcripts [3], October 12, 1977; Series 1 (Box 5, Folder 3)
- Senate Hearings: Labor Union Insurance Investigation Transcripts [4], October 17, 1977; Series 1 (Box 5, Folder 4)
- Senate Hearings: Labor Union Insurance Investigation Transcripts [5], October 18, 1977; Series 1 (Box 5, Folder 5)
- Senate Hearings: Labor Union Insurance Investigation Transcripts [6], October 19,1977; Series 1 (Box 6, Folder 1)
- Senate Hearings: Labor Union Insurance Investigation Transcripts [7], October 18, 1977; Series 1 (Box 6, Folder 2)
- Senate Hearings: Labor Union Insurance Investigation Transcripts [8], October 28, 1977; Series 1 (Box 6, Folder 3)
- Senate Hearings: Labor Union Insurance Investigation Transcripts [9], November 2,1977; Series 1 (Box 6, Folder 4)
- Senate Hearings: Fritzsimmons Testimonial Corrections and Correspondence, November 2, 1977-January 24, 1978; Series 1 (Box 6, Folder 5)
- Senate Hearings: Permanent Subcommittee on Investigations-Hotel Employees and Restaurant Employeees Union Transcripts, September 28, 1983; Series 1 (Box 7, Folder 1)
- Senate Hearings: Statement of Herman Leavitt, General Secretary-Treasurer of the Hotel and Restaurant Employees Union, Septeber 26-29,1983; Series 1 (Box 7, Folder 2)
- Senate Hearings: Correspondence and attache materials prepared for Testimony of Herman Levitt before Subcommitee on Investigations, December 5, 1973-September 29, 1983; Series 1 (Box 7, Folder 3)
- Senate Hearings: AFL-CIO Report on Joseph Hauser, prepared for permanent Subcommittee on Investigations, September 8-9, 1983; Series 1 (Box 7, Folder 4)
- Senate Hearings: AFL-CIO Report on Joel Keiler, prepared for the permanent Subcommittee on Investigations, September 8-9, 1983; Series 1 (Box 7, Folder 5)
- Senate Hearings: Attachments to AFL-CIO on Joel Keiler, prepared for the permanent SubCommittee on Investigations, September 8, 1983; Series 1 (Box 7, Folder 6)
- Senate Hearings: Materials on Oversight of the Motor Carrier Act of 1980 [1], September 12-21, 1983; Series 1 (Box 7, Folder 7)
- Senate Hearings: Materials on Oversight of the Motor Carrier Act of 1980 [2], September 21, 1983; Series 1 (Box 8, Folder 1)
- House Hearings: Statement of Ray Schoessling, Secretary-Treasurer of the Teamsters, before the Labor-Management Relations and Labor Standards Subcommittee of the Committee on Education and Labor, October 5, 1983; Series 1 (Box 8, Folder 2)
- Senate Hearings: Statements of John L. Barnhart, Craig Woodhouse, and Donald J. Wheeler before the Subcommittee on Investigations, January 31, 1984; Series 1 (Box 8, Folder 3)
- Senate Hearings: Statements before the Subcommittee on Investigations concerning Organized Crime in the Great Lakes region, January 25-31, 1984; Series 1 (Box 8, Folder 4)
- Senate Hearings: Teamsters Statement on S.462-Hobbs Act Amendment, May 18, 1984; Series 1 (Box 8, Folder 5)
- Senate Hearings: Materials for Hobbs Act Proposal to overturn Emmons, May 7-August 27, 1984; Series 1 (Box 8, Folder 6)
- Senate Hearings: Hearings on Labor Violence before the Committee on Labor and Human resources Transcript, February 28, 1985; Series 1 (Box 8, Folder 7)
- Senate Hearings: SubCommittee on Investigations Transcript-Government's Ability to Combat Labor Racketeering [1], November, 1981; Series 1 (Box 9, Folder 1)
- Senate Hearings: SubCommittee on Investigations Transcript-Government's Ability to Combat Labor Racketeering [2], November 3, 1981; Series 1 (Box 9, Folder 2)
- Senate Hearings: Oversight Hearing on Department of Labor's Handling of the International Longshoremen Association and the Teamsters Local 945 Transcript, May 27,1982; Series 1 (Box 9, Folder 3)
- Senate Hearings: Oversight Hearings on the Teamster Union Focusing on the Substance of S. 336, proposed Labor Management Racketeering Act, and Central State Settlement Matters Transcript, June 7, 1983; Series 1 (Box 9, Folder 4)
- Senate Hearings: Correspondence and Materials (files and receipts) related to testimony of Teamster President Jackie Presser, July 17, 1973-September 20, 1983; Series 1 (Box 9, Folder 5)
- Senate Hearings: Permanent Subcommittee on Investigations-Hotel Employees and Restaurant Employees International Union Hearings, unrevised and unedited transcript, September 20, 1983; Series 1 (Box 9, Folder 6)
- Senate Hearings: Permanent Subcommittee on Investigations-Witness statements and news clippings on Organized Crime and the Hotel Restaurant Employees Union, September 15-20, 1983; Series 1 (Box 9, Folder 7)
- Hearings Before the Committee on Labor and Human Resources, "Labor Department Erisa Compliance", February 23, 1982; Series 1 (Box 10, Folder 1)
- United States of America vs Dorfman, Williams, Lombardo, O'Malley, Massa: AM Session, October 28, 1982; Series 1 (Box 10, Folder 2)
- United States of America vs Dorfman, Williams, Lombardo, O'Malley, Massa: PM Session, October 28, 1982, Series 1 (Box 10, Folder 3)
- Vincent Trerotola Interview, incomplete copy, ND; Series 1 (Box 10, Folder 4)
- Deposition of Joseph Trerotola, August 9, 1988; Series 1 (Box 10, Folder 5)
- Ron Carey Property Transaction Summaries, Charles F.C. Ruff to Charles M. Carberry, April 1994; Series 1 (Box 10, Folder 6)
- Declaration of Barbara Carey, April 19, 1994; Series 1 (Box 10, Folder 7)
- Proposed Charge Against IBT Local 804 Member William Cardinale, May 20, 1994; Series 1 (Box 10, Folder 8)
- Correspondence Between Ron Carey and Thomas R. Donahue of AFL-CIO, June - July, 1994; Series 1 (Box 10, Folder 9)
- Strategy Memo: Opponents of Teamster Reform Plan to Use the "Threat of Raw Power and Fear"... by Forcing Ouster... of First Directly Elected President, July 25, 1994; Series 1 (Box 10, Folder 10)
- interview with Jesse Beckman Owner, Coronado Construction, July 27, 1994; Series 1 (Box 10, Carton 11)
- Charges brought against Leroy Ellis, 1992-1994; Series 1 (Box 10, Folder 12)
- Sworn Testimony of Ed Burke, February 1, 1994; Series 1 (Box 10, Folder 13)
- Sworn Testimony of Ronald Carey, February 15, 1994; Series 1 (Box 10, Folder 14)
- United States vs International Brotherhood of Teamsters Sworn Testimony of Ronald Carey, May 19, 1994; Series 1 (Box 10, Folder 15)
- Ron Carey Campaign Materials for IBT Presidency Reelection, June 1996; Series 1 (Box 10, Folder 16)